CHIYO KANO

Senior Full Stack Engineer

@ Devel_Master@outlook.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Engineer

Self-Freelancing

02/2022 - Present

[React.js | Next.js | Vue.js | Nuxt.js | TypeScript | Tailwind CSS | Node.js | Firebase | MongoDB | Laravel | WordPress | Python | Django | Web3]

- Due to the pandemic, I had to transition to remote work, and I discovered that it
 was an exciting and efficient method of working. I thoroughly enjoyed the
 experience and found it to be highly productive. I always strive to build longterm professional relationships with my clients.
- My mission is to continually improve each subsequent project, surpassing the
 quality of the previous one. This commitment has resulted in a remarkable 70%
 repeat hire rate, and I have had the privilege of working with certain clients for
 over 7 years. This is more than just a job to me. It is my life's passion.

Full Stack Engineer

Broadlume

= 07/2020 - 01/2022

[React | Gatsby | GrapthQL | Bootstrap | UI/UX Design]

- Developed a website to introduce the flooring industry and announce conferences on flooring technology
- Revised and updated the UI/UX design based on development needs
- Implemented the UI/UX design using React Gatsby and Bootstrap
- Tracked and fixed bugs and issues using GitHub as an issue tracking board

Senior Software Engineer

Tiny Talk

= 11/2018 - 06/2020

[React | Redux | Flutter | React Native | Firebase | PostgreSQL]

- Developed several apps that allows random one-to-one or group video chats that last seven minutes.
- Implemented a server-less back-end solution using Firebase Authentication.
- Built a mobile app and implemented a complicated UI/UX design using Flutter.
- Implemented one-to-one and group video calls on the app using Agora RTC Engine.
- Implemented deep linking to channels and video calls using Firebase Dynamic Links.

Full Stack Developer

Kiskoo

= 06/2017 - 10/2018

[HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Bootstrap | PHP | WordPress | Laravel | React | Jira]

- Developed a website to satisfy the needs of different sectors of the Dominican market including the movie music technology automotive sports tourism fashion and other industries.
- · Tracked and fixed bugs and issues using Jira a reporting tool.
- Developed several subdomains using WordPress CakePHP, React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.
- Implemented search engine optimization using Google Tag Manager and Ahrefs.
- Implemented banner, interstitial, and reward ads using Google Ads.

SUMMARY

I am a passionate senior full stack engineer with over 7 years of experience in software engineering. Always love challenges and hard working to achieve goals. Have advanced knowledge of multiple programming languages, frameworks and extensive familiarity with several database structures.

Working as a senior developer, lead developer, I have built several successful websites, mobile apps, and DeFi platforms for a large number of users, and have successfully completed several projects involving various technical fields depending on the business idea of the client.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree, Computer Software Engineering

Tokyo International University

= 04/2013 - 03/2017

SKILLS

Web Frontend

HTML	CSS	Java	Script	JQuery
TypeScript		Bootstrap PHP		
WordPress		React	Vue	Angular
Next	Nuxt	_		
Web Bac	kend			

Golang Django NodeJS/Express

Shopware

Python

NestJS ASP.NET

Mobile App Native

PHP/Laravel

Android:Java Kotlin Swift

Mobile App Cross-Platform, Hybrid

Flutter React Native Xamarin

SKILLS

DB, Could Services

MySQL **SQLite** MongoDB

PostgreSQL AWS **Google Maps**

Firebase Twilio

UI/UX Design

Figma Adobe XD Photoshop

LANGUAGES

English Fluently

